[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rose hips, the fruit of the rose plant, are rich in what vitamin?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin C", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin A", "Vitamin D", "Vitamin B5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these famous baseball players became the first major league player to hit two grand slams in one game?", "correct_answer": "Tony Lazzeri", "incorrect_answers": ["Babe Ruth", "Lou Gehrig", "Bobby Bonds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does ZZZ mean in Internet slang?", "correct_answer": "tired or bored", "incorrect_answers": ["zz top is great", "zero, zilch, zip", "theres a bee in my house"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This group was formed in Detroit, Michigan and its original members were Otis Williams, Melvin Franklin, Paul Williams, Elbridge Al Bryant, and Eddie Kendricks.", "correct_answer": "The Temptations", "incorrect_answers": ["The Drifters", "The Coasters", "The Juve Five"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Has anyone landed an aircraft or helicopter on the summit of Mt. Everest?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the cat in Edgar Allen Poes short story The Black Cat?", "correct_answer": "Pluto", "incorrect_answers": ["Midnight", "Neptune", "Blackie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these architectural styles is the earliest?", "correct_answer": "Greek", "incorrect_answers": ["Gothic", "Renaissance", "Roman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which skeletal muscle is used in blowing, whistling, and smiling?", "correct_answer": "Buccinator", "incorrect_answers": ["Orbicularis oculi", "Mandibular", "Masseter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kenny Rogers starred in a western series about a river boat gambler.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1999 movie, a local Game Warden teams up with a paleontologist to find an unknown creature terrorizing a small town.", "correct_answer": "Lake Placid", "incorrect_answers": ["Teeth 2: Revenge of the Croc", "Alligator", "Crocodile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ancient Greeks also had their bubble gum. They chewed the resin of this tree to clean their teeth and freshen their breath.", "correct_answer": "Mastic tree", "incorrect_answers": ["Ash tree", "Olive tree", "Pine tree"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many young can an adult aardvark have at one time?", "correct_answer": "only 1", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "up to one dozen", "3"]}]